A Finding Aid to the Chaim Gross Papers, 1920-2004, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence, 1926-1997; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 8.75 Linear feet Boxes 1-9, 22
  - Squadron, Howard M., circa 1966-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Stambler, Arthur, 1974-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - State of Israel Bonds, 1951-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - State of Israel Bonds, 1974-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - State Unversity College, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - State University of New York, 1951-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Stearns, Bear, 1973-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Stein, Ros and Joe, circa 1972-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Stephen Wise Free Synagogue, 1974-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Stern, Claire and I. Jerome, circa 1964-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Sterne Family, 1962-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Stone, Sybil, 1979-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Strauser, Sterling, 1941-1946; 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Strauss, Claudia, circa 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Syracuse University, 1964-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - S, General: S.-Sa, 1941-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - S, General: Scha-Schn, 1938-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - S, General: Scho-Se, 1938-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - S, General: Sh, 1938-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - S, General: Si, 1956-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - S, General: Sk-Sn, 1942-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - S, General: So-Spe, 1936-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - S, General: Spi-Ster, 1939-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - S, General: Stevens-Sy, circa 1950-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Includes two cards and a letter from James Johnson Sweeney.
  - Tarbell, Roberta K. (Bobbi), 1976-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Tavelli, Edna, circa 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Tel-Aviv Museum, circa 1952-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Temple Beth El, Birmingham, MI, 1974-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Temple Beth Israel, Phoenix, AZ, 1974-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Temple Shaaray Tefila, 1965-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Temple Sinai, Pittsburgh, PA, 1968-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Tenenbaum, Shea, circa 1941-circa 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Toledo Museum of Art, 1947-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Topper, Victor/Beth Tzedec Art Committee, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Treasury Relief Art Project, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Treasury Relief Art Project, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Treasury Relief Art Project, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - T, General: Ta-Te, 1949-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - T, General: Th-Tu, 1940-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Union of American Hebrew Congregations, 1948; 1968-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - United Cerebral Palsy of New York City, Inc., circa 1967-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - United Jewish Appeal (Various Divisions), 1956-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - United Jewish Appeal, Federation Joint Campaign, 1976-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - United Nations, 1960-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - United Nations Children's Fund (UNICEF), 1967-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - United Nations, Commemorative Stamps, "Namibia", 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - United Nations, Commemorative Stamps, "New International Economic Order", 1979-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - United Nations, Commemorative Stamps, "International Conference on Population", 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - United Neighborhood Houses of New York, Inc., 1951-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - United States Information Agency, circa 1959-circa 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - University of California, 1948; 1966-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - University of Connecticut, 1970-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - University of Georgia, 1957-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - University of Haifa, 1968-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - University of Illinois-Krannert Art Museum, 1971-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - University of Minnesota, 1946-1947; 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - University of Wisconsin, Eau Claire (Kenneth Campbell), 1967-1968; 1980-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - U, General: Uh-United, 1935-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - U, General: Universal-Ut, 1947-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Valentin, Curt/Bucholz Gallery, 1942-1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Van De Bovenkamp, Hans, circa 1978-circa 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Van Veen, Felicia and Stuyvesant, circa 1967-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Viener, Saul, 1977-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1945-1947; 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Vogel, Julius, circa 1970-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - V, General, 1928-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Walden School, 1958-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Walker Art Center, 1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Wang, Robert, International Synagogue Commission, 1971-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Washington Hebrew Congregation, 1976-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Wayne, Irving, circa 1957-circa 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Weingberg, Martin S., 1975-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Weinberger, Dave and Sabina, circa 1967-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Weinstein, Lewis and Selma, 1969-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Weintraub, Rhoda K., circa 1963-circa 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Westchester Reform Temple, 1967-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Westmoreland County Museum of Art, 1964-1965; 1977-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - White House Invitations, 1975-1976; 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1933-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1963-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Wichita State University, 1971-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Wien, Ellen and Sidney/Atlanta Art Institute, circa 1959-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Wiltwyck School for Boys, 1966-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Winter, Elmer R. and Nannette, 1968-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - WNET/Channel 13, 1976-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Wohlgelernter, Israel, circa 1967-circa 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Womens Campaign for UJA and Federation Art Auction, 1975-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Women's League for Israel, 1964-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Women's League for Israel, 1975-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Worcester Art Museum, 1956; 1974-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - World Federation of United Nations Association, circa 1973-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Writers and Artists for Peace in the Middle East, Inc., 1971-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Wunderman, Lester, relating to Eliot Elisofon, 1971-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - W, General: Wa, 1947-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - W, General: Wea-Wei, 1949-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - W, General: Wel-Wh, 1939-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - W, General: Wi, 1942-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - W, General: Wo-Wy, 1940-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Yeshiva University, 1967-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Yeshiva University, Albert Einstein College of Medicine, 1965-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Yochehlson, Kathryn, 1966-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Young Israel of Oceanside, 1965-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Y, General, 1934-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Zionist Organization of America, 1976-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Zorach, Marguerite and William, circa 1938-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Z, General, 1948-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - First Names Only, A, 1966-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - First Names Only, B, 1937-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - First Names Only, C, 1945-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - First Names Only, D, circa 1971-circa 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - First Names Only, E, circa 1963-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - First Names Only, F-G, circa 1950s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - First Names Only, H-I, 1937-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - First Names Only, J, 1936-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - First Names Only, K, circa 1960-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - First Names Only, L, 1942-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - First Names Only, M, 1943-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - First Names Only, N, circa 1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - First Names Only, P, 1946-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - First Names Only, R, circa 1960s-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - First Names Only, S, 1943-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - First Names Only, T, circa 1960s-circa 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - First Names Only, Y-Z, 1946-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Illegible/No Name, circa 1930s-circa 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Illegible/No Name, 1940-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Illegible/No Name, 1974-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Condolence Letters, A-D, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Condolence Letters, E-H, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Condolence Letters, I-P, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Condolence Letters, R-S, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Condolence Letters, V-Y, 1991, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Condolence Letters from Institutions, A-W, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Condolence Letters, No Name/Illegible, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Condolence Letters, First Names Only, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Oversized Grooms, Mimi, Red and Family from Box 3, Folder 63, Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Writings and Notes, 1938-circa 1980s; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 0.25 Linear feet Boxes 9-10
  Series is arranged as two sub-series.
  3.1: Writings and Notes by Gross, 1938-circa 1970s
  3.2: Writings and Notes by Others, circa 1950s-circa 1980s
  - Writings and Notes by Gross, 1938-circa 1970s; 3.1; Archival Resource Key
    Writings and notes by Gross include a review and a copy of the American Federation of Arts publication Magazine of Art for December 1938 featuring Gross's first published article. Writings and notes about other artists are drafts of short statements about artists including Federico Castellon, Robert Matta, Bernard Simon, Moses Soyer, and Harvey Weiss, possibly written as recommendations or for announcements or catalogs. Also found are drafts of chapters for Gross's how-to book The Technique of Wood Sculpture, with draft labels and photos of artwork to be featured in the book.
    - Writings About Other Artists, circa 1950s-circa 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Published Article, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Review of Unidentified Publication, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Statements about Projects and Work, circa 1950s-circa 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - The Technique of Wood Sculpture, Chapter Drafts, circa 1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - The Technique of Wood Sculpture, Labels for Photographs, circa 1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - The Technique of Wood Sculpture, Labels for Photographs, circa 1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - The Technique of Wood Sculpture, Labels for Process, circa 1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - The Technique of Wood Sculpture, Labels for Wood Sculpture, circa 1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - The Technique of Wood Sculpture, Photos of Artwork, circa 1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - The Technique of Wood Sculpture, Photos of Artwork, circa 1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Writings and Notes by Others, 1950s-circa 1980s; 3.2; Archival Resource Key
    Writings by others about Gross include remarks made at dedications of his sculpture, and on other occasions when he received awards and include copies of essays by John I. H. Baur and Carol Drisko. Writings by Gross's brother, poet Naftoli Gross, include a typescript of a childhood memoir recalling Chaim's boyhood and coming to America, and poems about Gross.
    - Artist Statements, circa 1950s-circa 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Notes, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Writings About Gross, circa 1950s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Writings About Gross by Naftoli Gross, circa 1950s-circa 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Personal Business Records, circa 1936-1982; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 0.25 Linear feet Box 10
  The series includes lists of Gross's drawing and sculpture, and of his private art collection with insurance values.
  Lists of loans and loan agreements include many compiled by Forum Gallery, with dates of execution and dimensions of artwork. Some lists include prices and insurance values.
  Agreements include one with Maurice A. Melford granting Melford the rights to reproduce Secret and Acrobats; and an agreement granting permission to use photographs in a film.
  Receipts are for consignments, sales, loans, and gifts of artwork, as well as shipping receipts, and receipts for supplies. Appraisals are for twelve works of art by Gross for various recipients.
  Miscellaneous records include a 1942 statement on taxes which relates to Gross's monetary prize for his contribution to the Artists for Victory exhibition at the Metropolitan Museum of Art.
  - Agreements, 1948, circa 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Appraisals, circa 1950s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Certificates of Appointment to Provincetown Art Commission, 1965-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Lists of Artwork, circa 1960s-circa 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Lists, Miscellaneous, circa 1940s-circa 1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Lists of Loans/Loan Agreements, circa 1949-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Lists of Loans/Loan Agreements, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Lists of Loans/Loan Agreements, 1978-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous, circa 1936-circa 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Receipts, circa 1930s-circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Receipts, 1939-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Receipts, 1967-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Printed Material, 1925-2004; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; 3.7 Linear feet Boxes 10-14, 22, FC 24
  Printed material is arranged by type and chronologically thereafter. Series is arranged as two subseries.
  5.1: Printed Material About Gross, 1925-2001
  5.2: Printed Material About Others, 1942-2004
  - Printed Material About Chaim Gross, 1925-2001; 5.1; Archival Resource Key
    Printed material provides a comprehensive survey of the numerous exhibitions, teaching opportunities, professional events, and philanthropic endeavors in which Gross participated throughout his career.
    Announcements and catalogs are for solo and group exhibitions, lectures and symposia, award dinners, openings and receptions, dedications of sculpture, and other special events. Brochures and programs are for books and films by or about Gross, tours of his studio, and events at which Gross was honored or at which his artwork was presented or dedicated. Additional printed material relating to awards and honors received by Gross can be found in Series 1: Biographical Material and Series 2: Correspondence. Copies of catalogs for Sculptors Guild exhibitions from the 1930s to 2001 can also be found here.
    Art school brochures are for schools in which Gross taught, including the Cumington School, the Brooklyn Museum Art School, and the New Art School, established by Gross, Raphael and Moses Soyer, and Alexander Dobkin at 567 Sixth Avenue in New York City in 1939. They also include brochures for art programs in which Gross taught or otherwise participated, and auction catalogs for auctions for which Gross contributed artwork.
    Brochures and programs are for dinners and award ceremonies in which Gross was honored or at which his artwork was presented or dedicated. Also found are brochures for Gross's books and films, and brochures for tours of his studio. Copies of catalogs for Sculptors Guild exhibitions from the 1930s to 2001 can also be found here.
    The series also includes a motion picture film and a video recording of the documentary A Sculptor Speaks, and video recordings of Tree Trunk to Head and an NBC broadcast of The Two Chaims, featuring an interview with Chaim Gross.
    News clippings and articles provide a comprehensive survey of the publicity Gross received over the course of his career from the early 1930s to the 1990s and include multiple articles on Gross in English, Hebrew, and Yiddish newspapers, magazines, and journals.
    The series includes a copy of the book The Sculpture Relief of the Ten Commandments by Gross and Rabbi Israel Mowshowitz published by International Synagogue in 1973; and Improvisations published in 1953 and 1955 for the Artists Equity Masquerade Ball with reproductions of artwork by Gross. Reproductions of artwork include two posters for a Sculptors Guild Carnival with artwork by Gross, and a holiday card designed by Chaim Gross and signed by Chaim and Renee Gross.
    - Announcements and Catalogs, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, circa 1920s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, circa 1930s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1935-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, circa 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1943; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1944-1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1948-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1950-1951; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1955-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1958-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, circa 1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1960-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, circa 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1970-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1978-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1980-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1982-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1985-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, Educational Alliance, 1925-1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Announcements and Catalogs, Educational Alliance, 1953-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Announcements, Catalogs, Clippings on Juries and Panels, circa 1946-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Art School Brochures, circa 1930s; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Art School Brochures, 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Art School Brochures, 1971-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Art School Brochures, Educational Alliance, 1974-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 26)